NEHA PANDEY

Java Backend developer



™ nehushree0194@gmail.com

in LinkedIn 👩 GitHub 🥆 portfolio

Profile

Self-motivated, Ambitious, passionate Backend developer with proficiency in Java, Data structure and Algorithims, Driven to deliver the best in any situation. Problem-solving mindset and the ability to perform well in collaboration.1200+ hours of coding and hands-on experience in developing 3 fully functional applications.Looking forward to working as an accountable and competent employee in an exciting tech company.

Professional Experience

Campus ambassador representative(Internship), krayonnz ≥

pre sales associate, *Byjus* ☑ 08/2021 - 11/2021 | Bengaluru

Senior Business development Executive, Unacademy ☑ 01/2022 - 04/2022 | Bengaluru, Karnataka

Languages

Hindi

English



Certificates

- basic java with great learning 🛮
- CCC(Nielit)

Education

Full stck web development, Masai □ 05/2022 - present | Banglore, Karnataka

Master of Science, St. Andrew's degree college 07/2015 - 09/2017 | Gorakhpur, India

Technical Skills

HTML, CSS, Javascript, GitHub, Java, Data Structure and Algorithms

Interests

Music, Travelling, Dancing, Movies

Projects

KFC, individual project 10/2022 - 10/2022

- Individual project, created in 5 days.
- its a food delivery app.
- Used HTML,CSS and Javascript.
- Features working of this app-successful login log out page, registered on app, menu page, ordering page.

Apple Tv+, *Group project* □ 10/2022 - 10/2022

- This was group project.created by 5 members, created in 5 days.
- Apple TV+ is a streaming service featuring Apple Originals — award-winning series, compelling dramas, groundbreaking documentaries, kids' entertainment, comedies, and more — with new Apple Originals added every month.
- Features working-logo of Planettv+,Login and Sign Up functionality on navbar, search functionality on navbar, landing page themes, Home page with navbar and footer,API,heroku,localstorage, Admin login page and admin dashboard that remove and any add series on the landing page; user can check upcoming series, on the second page user can able to see any video, sign out functinality, if user will sign out then he will redirect to the Home page
- This project took 5 days to complete.this project uses HTML,CSS ,javascript,API,heroku for backend part